[Music]
hi
guys interesting to see such a huge
crowd uh I expect the last day of
fintech Festival first session I was
expecting a slightly thinner crowd so
thanks everyone for coming I'm Ian I'm
from presedential AI lab program hit uh
and here I'm sure all of you are
wondering today like what are we
unleashing right so have you seen all
across fintech Festival booobs from
every organization startups everybody is
talking about AI right and we here at
credential looking at the future of
insurance and how we can craft that
future with you so just a quick show of
hands right so get everybody up and
awake uh who is uh who has Insurance
products I hope everyone does okay and
then who has credential
products okay keep your hands up keep
your hands up okay uh my financial reps
will contact the rest of you that don't
have your hands up yeah so I I hope the
videographers are getting the photos uh
but I I think really we are here to
build for you know financial services
and products for every life for every
future and how does AI shape that right
and here's what we are trying to explore
here today uh especially and
representing the AI lab so obviously
I'll be using a lot of word AI in
today's sharing so we used AI to ask AI
what the future of insurance is with AI
right um we have a strategic partnership
with Google so I used Gemini the the sof
the their image uh creation generation
model to come up with this beautiful
picture right so I asked Gemini what's
the future of insurance you see a robot
obviously in a control center he is
managing maybe operations helping with
claims and then there's another image
generated which is a robot that's like a
financial rep you know talking to a
person I'm not sure if that's the future
we want right um I I love my agent you
know sitting down with me buying me
coffee you know asking me about my life
and then you know sharing about what's
the best product that we can use for my
future and I I think in this context
that's why we have to ask all of you and
not ask AI because if we ask AI they
will put themselves at front and center
of what they see the V vision of
insurance to be so what is the AI lab
right we are really here to accelerate
credentials adoption of machine learning
Ai and generative AI uh while also
obviously mean as an organization
driving our strategic priorities to
serve you as customers so the customer
is our compass and delivering better
customer experiences is definitely one
of our key areas in using AI uh in this
in this context it doesn't have to be
limited to insure Tech right because
this is across all
organizations that are service driven
and it might be even something that we
can adopt and learn from maybe the
hospitality sector where customer is
their key next is obviously a
distribution uh which is a huge part of
what credential does uh we have
Financial Representatives uh
significantly more than our corporate
staff and that is really where we want
to empower them to serve you better
because I would not want that robot to
be my financial representative instead
of that I rather have my financial rep
understand me holistically and serving
my needs along every step of my journey
lastly as a insurance company we are
looking at how we can increase our
access uh for you know people like
yourselves those that have not raised
your hands uh to healthcare and
financial services uh and Al cor
Insurance
products so all of you might be
wondering why AI lab right you mean is
this new to credential are you just
starting to use AI so that's definitely
not the case right uh we we do have
already used an implemented AI
experiences across uh organization in
Africa and Asia which is our Focus for
credential PLC uh but the main thing
here today is that we're not here as AI
lab just to look at the general
mainstream adoption of AI we are called
a lab for a reason right we are looking
at Next Level AI products that we can
then eventually deploy experimented
technologies that we use that we build
in-house that we work with Google as our
strategic Partners but also startups and
ihls and schools like yourselves that
will be able to join us in this journey
to present solutions to our business
units and then eventually scale it out
with our Center Excellence with our
group technology team and our AI team
and that will go flow down back to the
business units themselves so this is
what we believe right we believe that
with a successful implementation we need
four main areas uh enablement domain
expertise and IP AI talent and expertise
as well as the unique industry inside
that we have right so we have that big
you know Red Dot in the center but where
everyone else comes in the ecosystem
comes in and that's the answer for the
crossroad puzzle at our boo um the
ecosystem itself is really the
enablement where we have our data and
sandbox that we make available to all of
you to experiment on uh that you would
use that but also maybe co-create
sandboxes with other organizations have
domain expertise and IP in our area but
also for your yourselves to bring your
IP to us and hopefully to look at
investable Futures with you know
spinning in and spinning out of this um
businesses but also the AI Talent
expertise right I have a team that I'm
leading with with uh AI Engineers data
Engineers but we are limited in our
Resource as as a company as an
organization we don't have the expertise
that some of you here might have right
the phds that are looking at the new age
next you know generation AI uh as well
as the unique industry insights right so
as I was sharing just now you know could
be Hospitality that has best in customer
service right can we adopt that can we
adapt that so with this ecosystem that
we are working on uh I'm sure some of
you were here on the the first day where
it was loud and buzzing and a lot of
people around uh we had anou signing uh
with some of the ihls and institutes uh
with Asian Institute of digital Finance
we had with SMU School of computing
because we need The Talented expertise
of the Next Generation uh but also uh
you know Republic poly and other poly
technices and many many more in the
pipeline uh but not limited to
universities uh we do have uh working
relationship with some government bodies
as well as research foundations
and here today at fintech Festival we
are also calling for startups to join us
right so all this are new and exciting
and I think I haven't shared this but we
are newly launched um and we only
launching on the 19th of November so all
these are pre-work right and if you want
to be this Pioneers in starting this
journey with credential AI lab this is
where you hear of us today and at the
booth at Hall too so we want to turn
ideas into AI products we want to tap on
this AI talent and expertise but also to
accelerate development and Adoption of
AI uh within the organization and that
means you know potentially bringing your
solutions to life right and seeing it
used it as credential customers yourself
uh so obviously the ecosystem and the
Partnerships that we have will be
critical in driving this uh so this is
really our current working model and as
a brand new entity AI lab you know we
are working like a startup and that you
know changes from time to time but this
is really what we are already pushing
forth uh we have a cohort zero of five
use cases that we have built inhouse uh
even before we launch uh hopefully to
launch with cohort one uh so the cohort
one uh were problem statements that we
have gathered since uh uh three months
ago with our business units across Asia
and Africa so have gaed more than 150
submissions of their problems right so
business is very good at telling me this
is my problem right and then they propos
some of their AI Solutions we help
refine them we build them internally
with us and Google alongside and what we
do is we distill some of this problem
statements into challenge statements for
everyone in the audience in the public
our ecosystem to leverage on right so
for startups and students that's very
clear working models uh we are working
out working models for research centers
institutes you know PhD students uh but
really for students I don't think
students are here in this stage but for
students that are really looking to join
us to submit some of their fyp Capstone
projects we at credential allows and
support in terms of expertise technology
expertise mentorships and then for
startups because if you already have a
ready solution of nxgen AI solutions
that you can deploy to credential that's
where we will have give you access to
our sandbox to allow you to you know
play and test and experiment with some
of the data that we have set aside and
where the graduation and demo day is is
not really the kind of accelerated
accelerated demo days that you see um
it's not really about getting investment
right we are really getting the buyin of
the buus of the business units so we
present the solution that we try on open
source you know uh Microsoft you know
any of this different open AI Solutions
we get it from Google which they are
presenting a whole bunch of solutions to
our business units we present the
startups and you know uh suggestions and
solutions from students as well and then
bu business units that self decide which
benefits them the most right cheaper
better faster right and that's how we
keep ourselves honest in the adoption of
AI so with that um I think this is a
whole Suite of you know uh uh expertise
and you know support that we provide uh
mentorship uh specialized advice our
internal and external networks but also
the platform and infrastructure and data
that we can make it accessible to to
businesses organizations and yourselves
as individuals uh to eventually build
Solutions together and uh we do help
support with you know grants and funding
when necessary uh be it internally or
externally so well if you if you dare to
innovate with us or if you care to
innovate with us um I think I think do
do check out some of the challenge
statements that have been reviewed uh we
are working alongside some of our
partners to to guide you in this journey
uh so there are in this four strategic
areas that I earlier mention Health
which is uh a huge part of our insurance
uh wealth which is all more in
structuring your financial uh
Investments and future uh technology
powered distribution so that might not
be limited to Insurance itself because
that could be uh you know sales related
how do we help to get you know
information out customer data crms
driven versus our core insurance and
operations which is highly uh relevant
in building efficiency within our
organization uh so I'll leave you guys
with that uh if any of you have any
questions we have a boo at Hal to right
outside the future matter stage uh we
have a nice pink Little Giant that you
can take photos with uh so that really
is one of the use cases by our lead
generation team in presedential
Singapore that has adopted for leads
generation uh and they use gen to create
a illustration of your dream right so
that was how our business units have
adopted gen internally how our group AI
technology team helps to scale some of
these Solutions and where credential AI
lab sits today is to experiment New Gen
Next Level and AI that we will take
forth with our ecosystem so thank you so
much uh have a good day for the rest of
the day today and a great after party
after thank you